A Guide to the Governor Mark R. Warner, Press Office records, 2001-2006 (bulk 2002-2006)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. News clippings, 2001-2005 (Accessions 40484, 41071, 41693, 42464).
  - 2004 (Accession 41693)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 20 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 21 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 22 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 23 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 24 (Box 20, Folder 54)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 25 (Box 20, Folder 55)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 26 (Box 20, Folder 56)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 27 (Box 20, Folder 57)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 28 (Box 20, Folder 58)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 29 (Box 20, Folder 59)
    - News clippings, 2004 Nov. 30 (Box 20, Folder 60)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 1 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 2 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 3 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 4 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 5 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 6 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 7 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 8 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 9 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 10 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 11 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 12 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 13 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 14 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 15 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 16 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 17 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 18 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 19 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 20 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 21 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 22 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 23 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 24 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 25 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 26 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 27 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 28 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 29 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 30 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - News clippings, 2004 Dec. 31 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - 2005 (Accession 42464)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 1 (Jan. 2 missing) (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 3 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 4 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 5 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 6 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 7 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 8 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 9 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 10 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 11 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 12 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 13 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 14 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 15 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 16 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 17 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 18 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 19 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 19 (1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 20 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 21 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 22 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 24 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 25 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 26 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 27 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 28 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 29 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 30 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - News clippings, 2005 Jan. 31 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 1 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 2 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 3 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 4 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 5 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 6 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 7 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 8 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 9 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 10 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 11 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 12 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 13 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 14 (Box 22, Folder 46)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 15 (Box 22, Folder 47)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 16 (Box 22, Folder 48)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 17 (Box 22, Folder 49)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 18 (Box 22, Folder 50)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 19 (Box 22, Folder 51)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 20 (Box 22, Folder 52)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 21 (Box 22, Folder 53)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 22 (Box 22, Folder 54)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 23 (Box 22, Folder 55)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 24 (Box 22, Folder 56)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 25 (Box 22, Folder 57)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 26 (Box 22, Folder 58)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 27 (Box 22, Folder 59)
    - News clippings, 2005 Feb. 28 (Box 22, Folder 60)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 1 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 2 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 3 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 4 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 5 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 6 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 7 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 8 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 9 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 10 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 11 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 12 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 13 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 14 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 15 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 16 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 17 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 18 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 19 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 20 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 21 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 22 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 23 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 24 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 25 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 26 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 27 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 28 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 29 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 30 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - News clippings, 2005 Mar. 31 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - News clippings, 2005 Apr. (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - News clippings, 2005 May (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - News clippings, 2005 June (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - News clippings, 2005 July (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - News clippings, 2005 Aug. (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - News clippings, 2005 Sept. (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - News clippings, 2005 Oct. (Box 23, Folder 39)
    - News clippings, 2005 Nov. (Box 23, Folder 40)
    - News clippings, 2005 Dec. (Box 23, Folder 41)
- Series II. News summaries, 2003-2006 (Accessions 41072, 41239, 41692, 42461).
  News summaries are packets composed of articles and stories about Governor Warner and the activities of his administration, gathered from various news media from around Virginia and the Washington D.C. area. In most cases, the articles were printed off of websites. However, if only a hard copy of an article was available, it was photocopied and included. Many of the news summaries also contain descriptions of television coverage devoted to Governor Warner. The packets were distributed to the governor and his staff members on a daily basis, and vary widely in size and content.
  - 2003 (Accession 41072)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 2 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 3 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 4 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 5 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 6 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 7 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 8 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 9 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 10 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 11 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 12 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 13 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 16 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 17 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 18 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 19 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 20 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 21 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 22 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 23 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 24 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 25 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 26 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 27 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 28 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 29 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 30 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2003 Jan. 31 (Box 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 1 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 2 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 3 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 4 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 5 (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 6 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 7 (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 8 (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 9 (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 10 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 11 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 12 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 13 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 14 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 15 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 16 (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 17 (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 18 (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 19 (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 20 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 21 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 22 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 23 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 24 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 25 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 26 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 Feb. 28 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 1 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 2 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 3 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 4 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 5 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 6 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 7 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 8 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 9 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 10 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 11 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 12 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 13 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 14 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 15 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 16 (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 16 (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 17 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 18 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 19 (Box 26, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 20 (Box 26, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 21 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 22 (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 23 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 24 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 25 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 26 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 27 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 28 (Box 26, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 29 (Box 26, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 30 (Box 26, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2003 Mar. 31 (Box 26, Folder 32)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 1 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 2 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 3 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 4 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 5 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 6 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 7 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 8 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 9 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 10 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 11 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 12 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 13 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 14 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 15 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 16 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 17 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 18 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 19 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 20 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 21 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 22 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 23 (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 24 (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 25 (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 26 (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 27 (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 28 (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 29 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2003 Apr. 30 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 2 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 3 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 4 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 5 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 6 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 7 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 8 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 9 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 10 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 11 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 12 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 13 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 14 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 15 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 16 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 17 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 18 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 19 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 20 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 21 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 22 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 23 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 24 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 25 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 26 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 27 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 28 (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 29 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 30 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2003 May 31 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 1 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 2 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 3 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 4 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 5 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 6 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 7 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 8 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 9 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 10 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 11 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 12 (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 12 (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 13 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 14 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 15 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 16 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 17 (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 18 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 19 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 20 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 21 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 22 (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 23 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 24 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 25 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 26 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 27 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 28 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 29 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2003 June 30 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 2 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 3 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 4 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 5 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 6 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 7 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 8 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 9 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 10 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 11 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 12 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 13 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 14 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 15 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 16 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 17 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 18 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 19 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 20 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 21 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 22 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 23 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 24 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 25 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 26 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 27 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 28 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 29 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 30 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2003 July 31 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 2 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 3 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 4 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 5 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 6 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 7 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 8 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 9 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 10 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 11 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 12 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 13 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 14 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 15 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 16 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 17 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 18 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 19 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 20 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 21 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 22 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 23 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 24 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 25 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 26 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 27 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 28 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 29 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 30 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - News summaries, 2003 Aug. 31 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 1 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 2 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 3 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 4 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 5 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 6 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 7 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 8 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 9 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 10 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 11 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 12 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 13 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 14 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 15 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 16 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 17 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 18 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 19 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 20 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 21 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 22 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 23 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 24 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 25 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 26 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 27 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 28 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 29 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - News summaries, 2003 Sept. 30 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 1 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 2 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 3 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 4 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 5 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 6 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 7 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - News summaries, 2003 Oct. 8 (Box 33, Folder 8)